Claudia **Johnson**



Address: Baumertstrasse 13, 60386 Frankfurt am Main

Mobile number: +49 177 917 8730

Email:

claudiaj.501@outlook.com

Date of Birth: 31.03.1989

Civil Status:Married, no children

Citizenship:German & South African

Arrival in Germany: 02/2021

Portfolio:

https://www.flipsnack.com/69 B7EEFF8D6/design-portfolioclaudia-johnson.html

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/claudia-johnson-27513a1a0/

Short Profile

I have 5 years of professional experience in graphic design, along with 3 years in customer service in both retail and corporate positions, and 2 years in the print industry.

I am looking for to get back into the design field, as well as study further and expand my knowledge into the whole Adobe Suite and Web Development.

Professional Experience

07/2021 - Current

Sales assistant at Elbenwald GmbH – Frankfurt, Germany

- Greeting and serving customers from the moment they enter the shop.
- Advising customers and answering any queries they may have.
- Keeping customer satisfaction at the highest level.

03/2019 - 02/2021

Graphic Designer at Wright Millners dental suppliers - JHB, South Africa

- Dedicated designer for all company print material and digital marketing platforms and strategies.
- Chosen to source competitive pricing and quality of print marketing materials, due to yielding superior results to then-current approaches.
- CorelDraw and Photoshop.

03/2018 - 03/2019

Client Liaison at Remata Print & Communications (Photobooks department) – JHB, South Africa

- Engaged with clients, across all channels, to provide aid and knowledge on orders and any possible technical issues.
- Processed client orders and assisted in additional administrative duties.
- Inspected of submitted artwork to improve turnaround times and eliminate flaws, so as to maximize customer satisfaction.

02/2017 - 03/2018

Operations Supervisor at Jetline Print – JHB, South Africa

- Oversaw efficient coordination and sustained productivity of store operations.
- Arranged and provided training and mentoring for new staff.
- Established and maintained a superlative client experience.

Education

2010

First year BA Graphic design at Design School Southern Africa

2007

Matric Certificate with University Exemption at Edenvale High School - South Africa

Languages

German – B1

English - Native

Afrikaans - B1

Knowledge & Skills

- Programs: CorelDraw, Photoshop advanced knowledge.
- Programs: MS Word, MS Excel, MS Power Point, MS Outlook very good knowledge.
- Friendly and approachable with strong attention to detail.
- Adaptable and resourceful approach to duties.



Millners Dental Suppliers (Cape) (Pty) Ltd

1E Welbeloond Road, Equites Park, Atlantic Hills, Cape Farms Cape Town 7550, South Africa

To Whom it May Concern

Dear Sir or Madam,

I would like to recommend Claudia Johnson as a candidate for a position with your organization. In her position as Graphic Designer, Claudia was employed in our office from 2019 - 2021. Throughout her time with our organization, she demonstrated skills that would make her an excellent employee at your company.

Claudia did a terrific job in her position and was an asset to our organization during her tenure with the office. She has excellent communication skills, is well organized, can work independently, and is able to effectively multi-task to ensure that all projects are completed in a timely manner.

Because of her effectiveness, I even gave her additional responsibilities, including assistance in organising events. Claudia went above and beyond in such assignments, as she did in all tasks.

She would be an asset to any employer, and I wholeheartedly recommend her for any endeavour she chooses to pursue. Please let me know if you have any questions.

Sincerely,

Marketing & Internal Sales Manager
Wright-Millners

celeste@wright-millners.co.za

CAPE TOWN

1E Welbeloond Road, Equites Park, Atlantic Hills Cape Farms Cape Town 7550 South Africa

Tel: (021) 530 8800 Fax: (021) 531 1700

JOHANNESBURG

36 Monte Carlo Crescent, Kyalami Business Park 1684 PO Box 30721 Kyalami 1684 South Africa Tel: (011) 549 9600 Fax: (011) 466 4488

PORT ELIZABETH

26 Seventh Avenue Cnr Worraker Street Newton Park Port Elizabeth 6045 PO Box 34328 Newton Park 6055 South Africa Tel: (041) 365 2623 Fax: (041) 364 0354



AME OF STUDENT:	MS. CLAUDIA GOUWS				DATE:	201	0
UDENT NUMBER:	G01GJ0						
OURSE:	BA GRAPHIC DESIGN				YEAR	FIRST	
OOKJE.							1
NISSED HAND-IN'S	0	1	71%	0 72%		3 4	71%
ORK ETHIC:	72% 98%	69% 95%	97%	99%	1		97%
TTENDANCE:	90 /0	3370					
SUBJECTS	SEMESTER 1			SEMESTER 2			FINAL
	TERM 1	TERM 2	MID-YEAR MARK	TERM 3	YEAR MARK	EXAM	
GRAPHIC DESIGN 1	62	67	65	64	64	59	63
BASIC ILLUSTRATION	68	61	65	63	64	60	63
BASIC DRAWING	68	. 75	72	69	71	63	68
PRODUCTION THEORY 1	64	73	69	77	71	55	66
BASIC PHOTOGRAPHY	66	67	67	67	67	63	65
ART & DESIGN THEORY & RESEARCH 1	52	45	49	58	52	56	53
VISUAL COMMUNICATION 1	68	65	67	69	67	57	64
COMMERCIAL ART 1	64	66	65	63	64	57	62
TOTAL	64	65	64	66	65	59	63
CLUDICATE			ov to chiccesse	LILLY COMPLE	TE A SUBJECT		
LEAR	NERS NEED A MI	INIMUM OF 50	% 10 SUCCESSI	OLLI COMI LI	TE A SOBJECT		
COMMENTS:	W	ell do	ne Clo	udia	•		
DIRECTOR	<u> Xeme</u>	leig		COURSE	DIRECTOR		